Thirty-thousand two-hundred thirty rabbits.
Thirty-thousand two-hundred thirty-one rabbits.
Thirty-thousand two-hundred thirty-two rabbits.
Thirty-thousand two-hundred thirty-three...
Re-l! Vince!
Vince, you were late coming back from your
scouting, so Re-l got tired of waiting and left too...
Huh?
Re-l?
You came back?
I've been waiting like a good girl!
Not here...
Hmph...
I'm just gonna go.
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
It's open...
Are you infected with cogito too?
Are you hungry?
Are you okay?
I... I-I...
I have been liberated from my raison d'être.
I-I-I-I seek the reason why I-I-I am who I am.
"The reason why I am who I am"?
I've gotten rusty.
Vincent.
You...
Miss!
The Autoreiv Control Unit?
meditation  the place where time ends
Vincent Law...
Ah yes, he was clumsy, but got his jobs done.
I never would've thought of destroying Entourages,
but now I can say that Vincent took the right course of action.
You don't understand?
It's because we were totally dependent on
the Entourages that things turned out this way.
Everything began with the cogito virus, didn't it?
Once we get rid of the infected autoreivs in this city-
No, that's not it, Walt.
We never needed autoreivs in the first place.
Don't you agree, Miss?
Even though a lot of citizens have died,
they are unable to do anything about it.
Ever since cogito-infected autoreivs
abandoned their duties as Entourages,
the Central Management Bureau
has been completely dysfunctional.
Isn't that right?
Is it true that the Security Bureau Chief is missing?
Hey!
Don't be rude to the Miss!
Raul Creed has...
But what was that light?
Light?
The pillar of light we saw two months ago.
Ow.
Come to think of it, many strange things started happening
since the night we saw that pillar of light.
Please don't worry yourself.
It's just a rumor.
Hey!
In any case, it is in times of great hardship for Romdeau citizens
that we immigrants must continue to fulfill
our duties so that we may become model citizens.
Please give our regards to the Administrator...
Chief!
Three infected autoreivs have been found!
Distance: 400.
To your positions!
We will launch an assault on the Mainland!
Time for a cogito hunt!
Well, Miss.
Please be careful on your way back.
Time to hunt infections!
Let's get Romdeau back!
And where am I supposed to go back to?
They were living amidst destruction in almost pitiful ignorance.
What can they do?
Same goes for me...
Upon reaching Romdeau, Vincent Law vanished without a trace.
These past two days, whenever I saw him in the city...
he was in the form of Ergo PROXY.
It seemed as though he was possessed
by a grief that rejected all contact with others.
What was once divided must again become whole.
When Vincent becomes one with PROXY...
Will the resulting person be the Vincent I know?
And then, I would...
Die!
Those of you who are model citi-ti-tizens,
stay in-in-in-inside and wait in your homes
until further instructions-ns-ns from
the Citizen Information Bureau-eau-eau.
Going out without permission may result in penalty.
I'd been bored by the current
order in paradise and desired change.
Did my twisted desires
awaken the monster called Ergo that
had been slumbering within Vincent?
Did everything start with me?
Re-l Mayer.
Where are your primary care physician's papers?
Ask my Entourage for them as usual.
What's going on?
So many problems...
I have to process a lot of things.
So many people have died.
Did they get an infection?
Or is it-
It was a chore just getting the
immigrant sector quarantined too...
and now I have this much data related
to that ADW Project that I have to check.
It's enough to complain about.
Well, I just have to authorize them.
ADW Project?
This is our first time under martial law too.
Even if the Security Bureau now has control...
Oh, by the way, the Bureau Chief you spoke about...
He's a wisecracker, that's for sure. Real sharp.
Where is he... Where is Raul Creed?
No idea...
But being too sharp is a problem.
Think about the ones who have to deal with him...
I have so much more busywork.
What is my grandfather...
What is the Administrator doing?
Oh, I know.
I should ask you to pass this on.
Please take this.
This data from the Health Bureau
pertains to the side effects of ADW.
Please deliver this to the Administrator.
I dare not tell him this myself...
What do you mean?
It was a total failure.
The mortality rate was 90 percent, you see.
The name of the genius Daedalus Yumeno is now mud.
What need was there for us to change anyway?
Model citizens need only protect the order of the Dome.
It's business as usual.
We just need to do business as usual... the way we usually do.
Don't forget them tomorrow, okay?
Your primary care physician's papers.
Take care.
Dependent on Entourages, the
collective, and the Administrator for everything,
and ignoring the truth - so this is the model citizens' fate.
Re-l!
I've been looking for you.
Daedalus.
So this is where you were.
Always roaming around...
Now, come with me.
Daedalus?
Monad PROXY...
I'm the one who killed you.
But how could you have taken this so far?
Donov Mayer!
The answer is PROXY One.
PROXY One!
Are you sad?
These...
They're pretty.
Why do you not fear me in this form?
Why?
Why should I?
You have such a gentle face.
What do I need to fear?
They're a matched pair.
Are they both yours?
One... seems to be Monad's.
You loved Monad, didn't you.
I pity you.
Because I love Monad too.
Who are you?
I am Re-l Mayer.
What are you saying?
Oh, but I...
am Re-l Mayer!
I wonder what's wrong with me.
Oh, so that was Vincent!
That must be it!
Daedalus...
I'm sorry.
Re-l, you don't need to imitate that bad girl so much.
You are yourself.
In the end, I couldn't fulfill any of my promises.
I could neither capture the PROXY
we were after, nor collect the subject...
Re-l, are you still rambling on about that?
Acting as though you've overwritten
yourself with the previous model's data...
What are you talking about?
Did you steal data from a terminal to surprise me?
Goodness.
I dislike it when you do things like that.
Please tell me!
What's behind the rapid decrease
in population over such a short time?
What is the ADW Project?
I heard it from the Bureau Chief!
What did you do to the citizens?!
You're hurting me.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
What do you mean?
You're not my Re-l.
Daedalus...
I get it...
You're...
the traitor.
Re-l!
Come out here!
Daedalus!
You're hurting me. Let go!
Answer me!
How's it looking?
A lot of 'em.
Chief, that one looks familiar.
Let's see...
Oh my!
Looks like a chance for a special promotion!
With this, I'll finally redeem myself...
You didn't come here until now.
And now, it's too late.
What do you intend to do now?
The time has already ended,
Creator.
The Womb System has fallen silent.
You know why, don't you?
The absence of Monad... no, Vincent.
So Raul started saying that we don't need PROXIES if we change.
That's the ADW Project.
Put simply, it's body modification.
As if such a thing is possible.
Then, knowing it would fail, you-
By the way,
the pillar of light you spoke of... That's Rapture.
You see, Raul couldn't live with the fact that we were the losers.
Losers?
The winners, huh.
Since you're here, it must mean he is still alive.
Let me tell you something helpful.
The one who ordered the attack on you here wasn't Raul,
surprisingly enough.
What do you mean?
This is as far as I go.
Try asking the man himself.
Grandfather...?
Grandfather gave the order.
You are Raul's Entourage!
The Administrator loved.
The Creator founded Romdeau...
And created us.
He gave us autoreivs...
And gave us the ability to have children.
The Administrator hated.
Why do we exist?
Who will ease our solitude?
Why did you abandon us?
Why did you not love us?
The Administrator sought.
Not the Creator...
But the entity we seized...
Monad PROXY.
The Creator returned to us, unbeknownst...
As an immigrant from Mosk.
The Creator took Monad from us...
And departed once again.
The Creator thinks, therefore we are.
No matter how we thought, the Creator was already gone.
And now, he returns to be with us for the third time.
We desire...
The world does not exist where the Creator does not think of it.
We desire that you think of us.
We think, therefore we are.
We are the raison d'être.
We think-
What are you...
Doing?
Grandfather!
Piano!
I'm home!
Stop it, Vincent!
Is that your goal, Ergo PROXY?
Please stop, Vincent!
Grandfather!
Vincent...?
Raul Creed...
Vincent...
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
The jesters' tears, the Administrator's shell...
The days of love and hate come to an end.
The labyrinthine purgatory appears and opens its doors.
meditation  shackles